thinkbanking.co.uk 2015-06-07

# Thinkmoney privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement explains how Think Money Limited, and the companies within the Think Money Group (All About Money Limited, Freeman Jones Limited, Think Loans and Mortgages Limited, Think Insure Limited, Gregory Pennington Limited, Wilson Andrews Limited, Ideal Finance Limited, Intelligent Lending Limited, and Think Money Group Limited) (collectively “the Group”) collect personal data from you, and how we will use and store this information.

Please read this privacy statement carefully, as once you send us your information you will be deemed to have read and accepted this statement.

The Group would also like to provide you with information, including through email subscription to regular communications and mobile telephone, about their and other companies’ products and services that may be of interest to you. We would also like to pass your details on to other carefully selected companies so that they can send you information, including by email and mobile telephone, about their products and services.

#### Where we collect your personal information?

We will only collect personal information, including where necessary sensitive personal data, about you when you apply to us, and any additional information provided by you or others in various ways, including:

a) When you complete an application form or a contact form requesting a call back.

b) When you participate in market research, competitions and promotions provided by, or on behalf of the Group.

c) Information the Group receives from each other, from business partners, and from other organisations such as credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.

Please note that for quality and training purposes, telephone calls to our offices will be recorded and monitored.

#### What happens to the information provided/collected?

The personal information you provide may be used in a number of ways, for example:

  * Responding to your requests, enquiries or complaints.
  * For product administration and to notify you of any important changes or developments to the products and services we provide to you
  * For customer research, statistical analysis and to understand the effectiveness of our advertising
  * For crime detection, prevention, and prosecution and to keep our website safe and secure
  * For audit and debt collection
  * If false or inaccurate information is provided and fraud is identified, details will be passed to fraud prevention agencies
  * Law enforcement agencies may access and use this information

  * We and other organisations may also access and use this information to prevent fraud and money laundering, for example, when:
  * Checking details on applications for credit and credit related or other facilities
  * Managing credit and credit related accounts or facilities 
  * Recovering debt
  * Checking details on proposals and claims for all types of insurance
  * Checking details of job applicants and employees
  * Please contact us at privacy@thinkmoney.co.uk if you want to receive details of the relevant fraud prevention agencies.
  * We and other organisations may access and use from other countries the information recorded by fraud prevention agencies.

#### Joint Applicants

If you provide personal information about someone else, for example a joint application, you must only do so with the consent of the other person. If you enter into a product jointly with another person your data will be shared with the other person.

#### Sharing your data with third parties

If you submit a credit card, loan or mortgage application we may also make one or more credit searches for each applicant when making our recommendation and, the chosen lender may also search your record to verify your credit worthiness and identity. The credit reference agency will add details of any searches to your record which can be seen by other organisations that make searches and they may use it to help make credit decisions about you, to prevent fraud and money laundering and to trace debtors.

We may also share your information with other companies within the Group for the administration of any products or services provided to you by any company within the Group. They may also provide you with information about other products and services that they provide. If you have provided your consent we may also share your information with marketing agencies, who provide marketing services on behalf of the Group, to promote the products and services provided by the Group or other carefully selected companies.

We may also use or disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government law enforcement authority, or to enforce legal rights. 

Although we do not routinely transfer personal information outside the European Economic Area (EEA), we may be required to transfer your personal data to staff or to one of our suppliers who are based outside of the EEA. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

#### Safeguarding your personal information

We take the protection of personal data very seriously and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided.

#### Review, correction and deletion of information from our files

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information we hold about you is incorrect, or if you would like your personal information removed from our records please contact us by email at privacy@thinkmoney.co.uk and we will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We will keep your information unless you ask us to remove it. 

If you would like to request a copy of the personal data we hold please contact the Data Protection Officer using the email above or at the address below. Any request may be subject to a £10 fee.

Data Protection Officer  
Think Park  
Mosley Road  
Trafford Park  
Manchester  
M17 1FQ

### Other types of advertising

When you visit our website or similar websites our advertisements may be used by Google for the purposes of remarketing, and they may appear on other third party websites you visit across the internet for remarketing purposes. Google and other third parties will use cookies to tailor advertisements for website users based on their previous visit to our website. More information about cookies can be found below.

We do not have any control over the advertisements you see on other third party websites however you can request to opt out or customise these advertisements by using the [Google Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

### Cookies

When using this website, some information may be collected automatically using ‘cookies’. These are small text files which facilitate the processing of your data and enable us to analyse how the website is being used. Cookies can be temporary or permanent.

Temporary cookies form part of the security process while you are using the website; permanent cookies identify the link you used to find our website, check your browser so that we can make sure that our website and services work well with your computer and to help us monitor traffic on our website.

#### Why are cookies used?

They help visitors. Cookies allow sites to do things like provide personalised content and remember their log-in details and settings. You can turn them off - this won't stop a website from working, but it might mean it won't work as well as it could, or that you have to do the same thing more than once.

They help website owners. Cookies tell website owners things like: what search engine a visitor used to find the website, how often they've visited it, how long they've spent on it, and so on.

We’ve set out below the cookies that we may use and those that are set by third parties on our website.

Cookie | Name | Purpose | More Information  
---|---|---|---  
ClickTale | WRUID | This cookie is used to collect information about how visitors use our website and allows us to compile reports to further improve our website. | Click [**here**](http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html) for more information about ClickTale and how to disable this cookie.  
Google Analytics | _utma _utmb _utmc _utmz | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. They keep track of when a visitor enters and leaves the website and any search engines and keywords that are used, including any personal and/or sensitive data. | Click [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) for more information about google analytics and how to disable this cookie.  
Session Variables | ASP.NET_SessionId ASPESSIONID | These cookies are used to keep all information about the visitor's session of the website and are essential for the website to work. These expire when the browser is closed. |    
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE | This tracks a layout version that the YouTube applet will use when displayed on the website. |    
DoubleClick Cookies | test_cookie ID | These are 3rd party cookies served by DoubleClick. They serve adverts to visitors based on the websites they've been to previously. | Click [here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) for more information about DoubleClick and how to disable this cookie.  
Our Cookies | sitetrack | This is used to see if a user has visited our website for the first time. | Click here to disable this cookie.  
sitetrack2 | This is used to see if a person returns to our website. This cookie is only created if sitetrack is present. | Click here to disable this cookie.  
PCC Landing | This is used to find the route a user entered our website through. | Click here to disable this cookie.  
AppID | This tracks if a user revisits our website | Click here to disable this cookie.  
  
Except for essential cookies, all cookies will expire after 10 years.

#### Disabling/Enabling Cookies

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings on your browser and by clicking on the disable button below. Please remember though that disabling certain cookies may affect the functionality of our website.

None of the features of our website will be affected - giving you the full experience.

Disable

#### Deleting Cookies

If you are using Microsoft Windows Explorer:

  * Open 'Windows Explorer'
  * Click on the 'Search' button on the tool bar
  * Type 'cookie' into the search box for 'Folders and Files'
  * Select 'My computer' in the 'Look In' box
  * Click 'Search Now'
  * Double click on the folders that are found
  * 'Select' any cookie file
  * Use the 'Delete' button on your keyboard

If you are not using Microsoft Windows Explorer, then you should select 'cookies' in the 'Help' function for information on where to find your cookie folder.

We do not pass on, or sell cookies to any other companies. Further information on the use of and managing cookies can be found at http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

#### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to this privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

Close window
